Hello friends, how do I introduce you all?
Welcome back. So, in today's video,
we are again going to talk about stocks very well for you.
If you checked the previous
video, I had
told you about Axis Bank, I had told you that the
Devotion Hens Shoulder was performing in Axis Bank,
which would be
very profitable for that channel trade. If
you have taken entries, it is a very
good thing, but keep trailing your stop loss, there is a
lot of chance that it will turn out to be quite
good. You must have
told me earlier about SSC lot, growth
and the new line, if it breaks, its
postmortem will come back from the chart, that is why you have to
hold the app like this. Similarly,
for HDFC AMC, I had already told you
something about Varun Beverages,
where this tester was also happening, its
entry will be something like this. It
also has a turn in a similar way. There should be a lot of break in it.  A
postmortem will happen because the
voltage is quite high and they have already reached a volume
peak, so there's a high
chance of a postmortem. If you haven't
taken an entry, you can take it back.
Now, in an earlier video, we talked
about "Friend World Not Done." There's
momentum in it. You'll see profit from your interview
today. The laptop has been
launched. Rings Plus, and it even
reached here. Cornflour, so I've
now removed it. The
first topic we're going to look at today is Butt
India. I told you about this point I
hit. I told you there's a
high chance you'll get tested on it. The people who are
amazing here will be of animals.
Due to the stoploss, there will be a pre-
test, then you should do it. If you
keep following my videos, you'll keep getting updates.
And if you think
you'll get a chance, then definitely subscribe to Shaan. At
this level, as I
mentioned, this test was happening.
You can take entries there. There's a high
chance of a postmortem from here.
And you have to find the target. This is the first one.
You're going to get to this level. After that,  The
work of Narration is also to find the target,
so simply now you can use PowerPoint, can you
press f5, a minute ago I
told you about the tower, I
told you that I have kept the entry from this level,
now you can check yesterday's video, in that I
told you that I have kept the entry
and you have already seen yesterday, if you
keep the entry then there is a lot of post-mortem,
today also there was a lot of opportunity, there is a chance for entry and tomato,
you can keep it by folding, so
today please see from
Aditya Birla Fashion, this trend line
report spirit was received, I have
taken entries, I have decided on Radha quantity, right
now it is very less quantity, I just have to make sure
that this is not a fake account, it can
break Israel,
your next target is this racing series which is going to be
healthy around 230 by 2030, right now by
taking this simple, there is a lot of
support here on this level, which
is cold, and wipe your eyes, there is a lot of chance of momentum coming
and today's next we are going to see
ITC was there, there was a lot of post momentum in ITC also,
after a day, a lot of time only
December 18 came, till then there was operation for a year and eight
months,
apart from the beginning of front puberty, there is a
lot of chance that rain or post mortem maya
may come back, when to add, keep this in your radar
also, today's job alerts and
we are going to see that jamna and there is a
lot of chance of getting into it, this lovely compound
resistance zone was a pre test,
and it has shown a lot of bottom, similar entries have
not been taken, wash can be added in it, the
post which I have got a lot of chance and torque is
quite good and if we talk about them, yesterday the
volume was very high and its and today it has been given
to Ritesh, so believe me, there is a
lot of chance in the post, everyone has to take entry, that is why
Balkeshwar can affair and the staff
which is made of two silks, okay, initial, so
if you think that I will get a chance then
definitely subscribe to my channel,
definitely press the like button on the video